ebilgames.com 2016-03-08

# Ebil Games - Privacy Policy

EbilGames (created and run by Artix Entertainment, LLC) provides family friendly entertainment to our users (Well, except for maybe that Deady game... it is pretty creepy). As a result, we are committed to protecting the safety and security of its online visitors and are sensitive to our user’s concerns about the safety of the personal information provided to us. We do not collect personal information on this site as it is a mini-games download site. 

**E-mail**  
By allowing you to send e-mail to us, we are not attempting to collect any personal information about you. We will only use personal information (such as name and e-mail address) contained in your e-mail to respond to your specific inquiry or comments in the e-mail. Although we may retain your e-mail for a period of time, we will not use any personal information contained in your e-mail for any purpose other than responding to your specific inquiry or comments. Whatever the activity may be, we will only collect information to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to fulfill your requests and our legitimate business objectives.

By using this site, you signify your assent to the EbilGames.com Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this site. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Please check back from time to time to ensure that you are aware of these changes. Your continued use of this site will signify your acceptance of these changes.

**Contacting EbilGames**  
If you need further assistance or have any additional questions or comments about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@ebilgames.com or write to us:

Member Services  
Artix Entertainment, LLC  
P.O. Box 2005  
Land O’ Lakes, FL 34639
